In this video we'll create a neural network for discovering the patterns in our data.
在此视频中 我们将创建一个神经网络 用于发现数据中的规律
After training, we'll be able to use the network to
训练之后 我们将能够使用该网络
classify the digits contained in new images.
分类新图片中包含的数字
Since our data points are vectors with 784 entries,
因为我们的数据点是有 784 个项目的向量
the input layer will have 784 nodes.
因此输入层将有 784 个节点
Let's start with two hidden layers each containing 512 nodes let's say.
我们先从两个隐藏节点开始 每个均包含 512 个节点
Our output layer has to distinguish between
我们的输出层需要在 10 个不同的数字之间进行区分
10 different digits and so I'll give it 10 nodes.
因此节点设为 10 个
In this lesson we'll always add
在这节课 我始终会在最后的全连接层上
a softmax activation function to the final fully connected layer.
添加一个 softmax 激活函数
It ensures that the network outputs an estimate for
这样可以确保网络会输出
the probability that each potential digit is depicted in the image.
图片描绘的是每个潜在数字的概率估值
We'll now specify this drafted model in keras.
现在我们将在 keras 中指定这个草稿模型
If you recall how we specified neural networks in the last lesson,
如果你还记得在上节课是如何指定神经网络的
this code shouldn't look too different.
那么这段代码看起来应该很相似
I've only added one new thing,
我只增加一行新内容
it's the flatten layer.
即展平层
This layer appears before you specify the MLP.
这一层出现在指定 MLP 之前
It takes the image matrix's input and converts it to a vector.
它获得图片矩阵的输入并将其转换为向量
In the model summary we can see that it outputs a vector with 784 entries.
在模型摘要中可以看到它输出了一个具有 784 个项目的向量
This model is great as a first draft but let's
对于首次创建而言 这个模型不错了
make it a little better using the tools that you learned about in the previous lesson.
但是我们将使用你在上节课学过的工具对其进行优化
We'll begin by adding a ReLU activation function to all of our hidden layers.
我们将向所有隐藏层添加一个 ReLU 激活函数
Remember that this function leaves
注意 这个函数不会处理所有正值
positive values alone and sends all negative values to zero.
并将所有负值处理为 0
We saw that the ReLU function helps with what's known as the vanishing gradients problem.
我们知道 ReLU 函数可以帮助解决梯度消失问题
By adding the ReLU function,
通过添加 ReLU 函数
we'll see that our model is able to attain much better accuracy.
可以使模型的准确率大大提高
This activation function will also be extensively used in convolutional neural networks.
该激活函数也广泛应用于卷积神经网络
If you train this new model,
训练该新模型后
you'll notice some evidence of over-fitting where the model does
你会发现某些过拟合现象
a really good job at predicting the digits and
模型能够很好地预测训练数据集中的数字
the training data set but it doesn't do so well on the test images.
但是测试图片的识别效果却不太好
You'll have a chance to check this out for yourselves soon.
你很快就能自己研究这一点
In the meantime in order to minimize over-fitting,
在此期间 为了尽量避免过拟合现象
we've learned in the last lesson that we can add dropout layers.
我们在上节课学到了 可以添加 dropout 层
We'll add a couple to this model.
我们将向该模型添加几个 dropout 层
Remember that the dropout layers must be supplied a parameter between zero and one.
注意 必须向 dropout 层提供 0 到 1 之间的参数
This value corresponds to the probability
该值对应的是网络中的任何节点
that any node in the network is removed during training.
在训练期间被忽略的概率
When deciding its value,
在设定该值时
it's recommended to start small and see how the network responds.
建议先从小的值开始 看看网络有何响应
Then you can increase it if you see that it's necessary.
然后如果觉得有必要增大的话 再增大这一值
We've chosen to set this parameter to 0.2.
我们选择将该参数设为 0.2
In the next video we'll continue to work with the model.
在下个视频中 我们将继续处理该模型